

UI/UX Designer

Contact

085799437007

rahmatraditya1234@gmail.

No.7, RT.10/RW.12, Kby. Lama Sel., Kec. Kby. Lama, Kota Jakarta Selatan

Social



Personal Website rahmatraditya.github.io



LinkedInRahmat Raditya

About

Use design tools to create user interfaces, user interactions, and interactive prototypes. Gather and evaluate user requirements in collaboration with product managers and engineers. Assist in executing all UI/UX design stages from concept to final hand-off to engineers. Skilled in Sketch, Illustrator, Photoshop, InvisionApp, and other relevant design tools. Knowledge in typography, styles, grid layouts and building UI design systems. Knowledge of user flows and user experience journeys. High emphatyze to user, skilled in Wireframing, Graphic Design, Web Design, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), and HTML.

Education

Computer and Network Engineering

Vocation High School 2 Klaten (2015 - 2019)

Course

Basic UI/UX by TutorTeknik (9 November 2019)

Learn the basics of design thinking from scratch to practice it at the same time.

Full Stack Designer by Buildwithangga.com (4 Juli 2019)

Create a fashion store website from research, ideation, wireframing, testing, design, and coding using the CSS Bootstrap 4 framework.

Experience

UI/UX Designer - Internship

Monggopesen.com (Februari 2019 - Januari 2020)

Designing a website or mobile based application for an e-commerce import from China.

UI/UX Designer

CSS 3

Koanba.com (Januari 2020 - May 2021)

Create a fashion store website from research, ideation, wireframing, testing, design, and coding using the CSS Bootstrap 4 framework.

UI/UX Designer (Freelance)

Orion Scope (April 2021 - Recent)

Online based Digital Agency. Design and develop websites for businesses and corporates. Helping all businesses to have digital and online presence.

Skills Wireframing Prototyping Layouting HTML 5 Tools Figma Invision Studio Adobe Ilustrator Bootstrap 4

Portfolio (Exploration)



Dribbble

https://dribbble.com/rahmatr



Bē Behance

https://www.behance.net/rahmatraditya1234

Portfolio (Project)

Social Commerse - Kipaskipas App

Social-commerce application based on Android and IOS. Which allows the user to be able to social media and shop.

Link: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.koanba.kipaskipas

News Website - Kipaskipas News

News portal website which later can supply news content to the fan application.

Link: https://news.kipaskipas.com/#/

E-Learning University - UNDIRA (Redesign)

Redesigning an e-learning website for campus in Jakarta. Make the website look more fresh and modern.

TONASE - Manage Shipping Cargo (SaaS)

Designing a SaaS based Web app which EMKL can use to manage their shipping business. Subscribe to a SaaS package that can be customized according to business needs.

Orion Scope - Landing Page

Landing page containing to inform important points and displaying some portfolio to clients.

Link: https://www.orionscope.id/

Teman Psikolog App

Mobile application that is used to find counselors to pour out all their heart's problems, and get opinions and suggestions on the problems they face. Choose a counselor then schedule and pay fees in one easy way.

Employee App

Applications to assist companies in managing their employees. Good absences, leave, work assignments to finances.

QC House Construction App

An application that is used to check newly built buildings per section such as foundations, pillars, roofs, to details such as ventilation, doors, and locks. Everything is recorded in a structured manner and can be monitored directly by the project supervisor.

NUCH Website

Website for a cosmetic brand, which a landing page, product details, includes cart and direct shopping in it.

TMS - Shipping Logistic App

Mobile application for couriers and warehouse staff to managing the delivery of packages between outlets to the consumer's destination address.

And Others.